<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guides on 第二届开源管理办公室年度峰会</title>
    <link>https://ospo.events/en/guide.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Guides on 第二届开源管理办公室年度峰会</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language><atom:link href="https://ospo.events/en/guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Visa Letter Request</title>
      <link>https://ospo.events/en/guide/visa_letter_request.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ospo.events/en/guide/visa_letter_request.html</guid>
      <description>For those needing a visa invitation letter, please refer to the instructions on this page. INSTRUCTIONS Before asking for a visa invitation letter, please check out the website of Chinese Visa Application Service Center for the visa application in your city. Please pay attention to the latest visa policy of China:
 144-Hour Visa-Free Transit Policy China has resumed the 144-hour visa-free transit policy, which allows people from certain countries to enjoy six days of travel to select areas of the country without applying for a visa beforehand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accessiblity</title>
      <link>https://ospo.events/en/guide/accessibility.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ospo.events/en/guide/accessibility.html</guid>
      <description>OSPO Summit strives to be a welcoming, inclusive, and accessible environment for all, regardless of ability.
Participants requiring special accommodations should provide details in their registration and/or by emailing us at cici@segmentfault.com. This information will be kept private and only be shared with individuals who need to know to secure these accommodations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://ospo.events/en/guide/code_of_conduct.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ospo.events/en/guide/code_of_conduct.html</guid>
      <description>Our Pledge We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual identity and orientation. We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convince Your Boss</title>
      <link>https://ospo.events/en/guide/convince_your_boss.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ospo.events/en/guide/convince_your_boss.html</guid>
      <description>Want to attend but not sure how to bring it up with your boss? We’ve created this sample email to help you explain why it’s important to attend OSPO Summit 2024. Feel free to use the full letter or pieces that work for you. See you in Shenzhen!
Download Template </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://ospo.events/en/guide/faq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ospo.events/en/guide/faq.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Slides Template</title>
      <link>https://ospo.events/en/guide/presentation_slides_template.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ospo.events/en/guide/presentation_slides_template.html</guid>
      <description>Make a presentation slide Please use the official template for PPT making.PPT template download:https://github.com/orgs/ospogroup/discussions/13
Session time is about 30 minute. It is recommended that you limit your presentation to 25 minutes, taking into account overtures and Q&amp;amp;A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms &amp; Conditions</title>
      <link>https://ospo.events/en/guide/terms_conditions.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ospo.events/en/guide/terms_conditions.html</guid>
      <description>Refund Policy If you must cancel for any reason please notify us via email at vivian@segmentfault.com. Refunds will only be issued for cancellations received 14 days prior to the first day of the event and may take up to 14 days to process. Please note that all refunds are subject to a 3% processing fee. You can cancel or modify your registration from your confirmation email.
Photo &amp;amp; Video Release I hereby consent to the photographing of myself and the recording of my voice and the use of these photographs and/or recordings singularly or in conjunction with other photographs and/or recordings for advertising, publicity, commercial or other business purposes for the organizer of the conference.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
